Three Great Laff Stars ! . . . more gags and gals . . . more songs and dances !
A Day at the Races is a comedy, music film directed by Sam Wood.
Doctor Hugo Hackenbush, Tony, and Stuffy try and save Judy's sanitarium by
winning a big race with a finicky horse owned by Judy's boyfriend Gil.
There are a few problems.
Hackenbush, who was recently put in charge of the sanitarium,
isn't really a doctor, he's a veterinarian.
Dr. Hugo Z. Hackenbush, played by Groucho Marx.
Tony, played by Chico Marx.
Stuffy, played by Harpo Marx.
Gil Stewart, played by Allan Jones.
Judy Standish, played by Maureen O'Sullivan.
Emily Upjohn, played by Margaret Dumont.
A Day at the Races is a 1937 American comedy film, and the seventh film starring the Marx Brothers
(Groucho, Harpo and Chico), with Allan Jones, Maureen O'Sullivan and Margaret Dumont.
Like their 1935 Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer feature A Night at
the Opera, this film was a major hit.
The film explores themes of veterinarian, musical, femme fatale.
The tone is lighthearted.